My body is hot. I'm panting for breath.
The blood's circulating
so rapidly inside my body,
my heart feels like it's about to burst.
When was it that I last felt this way?
It's the same rush I used to feel
when facing a few dozen enemies at once.
But this time, the situation
is completely different.
My body did move on its own, but...
why?
What in the world could have happened...
to cause my body to react in that way?
I want to know.
Good morning...
Whoa, it's all bagged up neatly!
I thought it would be best
to minimize the volume of garbage,
so I sliced it all up into small pieces.
Wow. It takes up half
the space it usually does!
Thank you, Ms. Servant.
Episode 2: You Want to Know.
I can't believe someone had the nerve
to leave this thing in front of my house.
Please Adopt Me
Just what the heck do they think we are?
Master Hitoyoshi, there appears to be a letter.
"I bought this dog at a pet shop
thinking it was a Pomeranian,
but it turns out it's a breed that
grows much larger. Whoopsies!
It's too big for my home,
so I decided to leave it at
a rich-looking family's house!
Take good care of it, 'kay?"
Talk about selfish!
And it pisses me off that
they're so flippant about it!
Jeez... What were they going to do
if we couldn't keep pets here?
Please Adopt Me
Right?
Are you going to adopt it?
Huh? Well, yeah. I can't just leave it here.
It's so small, and if it's left outside
in the middle of summer,
it's possible it could die.
And I can't think of anyone else
who might be willing to take it, so...
Even if it's small...
As long as the desire to live is strong enough,
you can cling to life, regardless of
who you are or what happens to you.
That's the instinct of an animal: to survive.
Saving a life solely out of pity
can have disastrous consequences.
That puppy was abandoned because
it was meant to be abandoned—
an existence that is not needed by anyone.
Such vulnerable beings are
doomed to die in the wild
if they are not forced
to become strong on their own.
If you carelessly save that life,
the consequences of your actions
may one day come back to haunt you.
Master Hitoyoshi, will you be able
to bear that responsibility?
Um... I don't really understand
that sort of thing, but...
Yesterday, when you saved my life...
It wasn't out of pity, right?
If we see a life in danger,
our human instinct causes our bodies to act
before we can even think. I'm sure of it.
Human instinct...
Besides, I understand
what it feels like to be left behind.
In any case, instead of standing around here,
let's finish taking out the trash and talk inside.
If we stay outside, this heat's
going to boil us till we're well-done.
You're so friendly and cute!
Do you want to try holding him, too?
No, I'm...
quite all right.
You've really been keeping your distance.
Not at all.
See? Look how fluffy he is!
Are you... afraid of dogs, Ms. Servant?
N-No... Well...
Just a little bit.
I really only am afraid of them a little.
Man, she's cute.
H-However, if it's an o-order...
If it's what you wish, Master Hitoyoshi, then...
You don't have to force yourself that much!
Why are you afraid of dogs?
When I was a child, the man
I once considered my mentor...
In the name of training,
he left me on a mountainside
filled with ferocious wild dogs.
Right... That'd traumatize anyone.
Hm, but that's going to complicate
matters with this guy, huh?
Man, what to do...
Man, what to do... What to do... What to do...
M-My apologies... for not being of any use.
Huh?! I wasn't blaming you or anything!
Just... I was thinking I might need
to ask you to bear with us,
since I wouldn't want him
to be left alone again.
Even if I were to search
for someone to adopt him,
it probably wouldn't go that easily,
and I'd hate to see him get
passed around like a hot potato.
Master Hitoyoshi,
on second thought, may I try holding him?
Ms. Servant, I'm really glad
you're trying, but seriously...
If you can't do it, that's okay.
Th-There's nothing... I can't... do...
He's been pretty well-behaved, too.
What part are you afraid of?
What part...
Those beastly claws.
Those ferocious fangs!
Those sharp eyes!
And such.
Sorry... When I look at him,
all I see is a big ol' mochi cake.
Mochi...
Are you referring to that
chewy confection made from rice?
Yep, that's the one.
I think most people would feel the same way.
He's just play-biting!
It's not for real, so calm down!
Don't throw him!
Y-You did a good job trying.
I'm sorry for being so pathetic.
Hm?
Oh, hey... Are you teething, buddy?
You mustn't do something that dangerous—
I'm fine!
All right, let's go out for a bit.
Y-Yes, sir.
Animal Hospital
An animal hospital...
Yep.
He seems fine, but I figured we should
get him checked, just in case.
Could you stop by the shop
next door for me, Ms. Servant?
Yes, sir.
Chewing Bone
Fresh
She's seriously trying her best for you, buddy.
Doesn't that make you happy?
Thanks for picking out the stuff
I asked for, Ms. Servant.
Master Hitoyoshi, you truly are a kind person.
Huh?
Up until now, there was no one
like you in my world.
Where I was, failure was not an option.
That's probably why
every time you're kind to me,
I feel a certain distance from you,
Master Hitoyoshi.
Up until now, all I had to do
was what was asked of me.
But the things you ask of me are all things
I'm experiencing for the first time, and...
every time, regardless of how
hard I try, I mess up and fail.
I... don't understand.
How can I become someone
you need, Master Hitoyoshi?
It's not as though I haven't been
considered unneeded before.
In the world I lived in, we had to fight over
a dwindling number of places to belong,
like a game of musical chairs.
For pawns like us,
it didn't matter to those in power
what age or gender you were,
as long as you had the skills.
If I wanted somewhere to belong,
there was only one thing I needed to do.
But it's different here.
Yokoya
What I'm capable of, everything I did
to get here—it all amounts to nothing.
If only I could have met you
the way that puppy did...
If only I'd come to know sooner just how much
this world overflows with warmth...
I might have been able to be
who you really want me to be.
Am I truly allowed to be here?
Don't you think one such as me is unneeded
in this world filled with the light of day?
Ms. Servant, could it be that...
Hey, don't pull while I'm talking!
It just sounds like you want to quit your old
job and be a normal girl. Isn't that right?
No more killing?
That's what I got from that, anyway.
H-Hey... Oh, man. I'm all tangled up now.
Whoa, hey! Stop moving!
Quit being an assassin and... be a normal...
It had never even crossed my mind.
Being an assassin was my sole identity.
That's what I was told all along—that in order for someone like me to be needed,
I needed to kill, and kill, and kill.
That killing people was the only way.
But if...
Wow!
The sunset's super pretty!
If I can find a sense of belonging
outside of killing people,
will I be able to get to know him—
to get to know this warm, sunny world better?
You know, when you first came to my house,
I was really scared of you.
What?!
Well, I'm not used to having
assassins around, you know?
But being with you made me
realize that I was wrong.
Ms. Servant, you're actually
a really good girl!
A good girl. A good girl...
Master Hitoyoshi.
What do I need to do in order
to become a normal girl?
Huh...
Um... That's a hard question.
Oh, but I thought of something.
You seem like you're always worried
about making mistakes,
but you said it yourself, remember?
That everything you've done since
coming here has been new to you.
When you're doing something for the first time,
I think it's normal to make mistakes.
It's true... This method cuts the cabbage
more efficiently and evenly.
There's no need to mentally prepare, either.
Maybe being normal is about being efficient.
Okonomiyaki...
I wonder what kind of food it is.
I heard that the sauce is
the main part of the dish, but...
It seems it's not something fried,
but you need cabbage. Hm.
Come to think of it, I feel the cabbage
would go well with the sauce.
Impossible!
How could he manage to sneak up behind me?!
Y-You...
You're no mere dog, are you?!
Are you... hungry?
I was able to understand how he was feeling.
This must be part of being normal, as well.
I'm home!
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing...
Oh, you fed him! Thanks!
Yes, sir...
I'm happy for you. Is it yummy?
You sure can eat. Are you okay?
Your stomach's all round and squishy!
Just like mochi!
Mochi... Mochi...
Oh, it just dawned on me.
What?
Your name can be Agemochitaro!
(Mochi is delicious!!!)
What do you think?
I think it's a wonderful name.
Oh! You like it, too, huh?
It's easy to understand, and on top of that,
I sense something intimidating from it.
You think so?
You chopped the cabbage for me, huh?
Thanks! That's a big help.
No, this is nothing...
You're starting to get used to being a maid!
I'll do the rest!
Oh, what's up, Agemochitaro? You want to play?
Sorry, buddy. Wait until after dinner, okay?
Hey, hey.
Would you like me to watch over him?
What?! Are you sure?
You don't have to force yourself...
I'll be fine!
Fresh
Made In Japan
Low lipids and easy to eat
Delicious and healthy balance
I want to be normal.
You've said it yourself, Master Hitoyoshi.
He's just a well-behaved puppy,
and yet, all I see is a ferocious wild dog.
But everything I know about being normal
is what you have told me, Master Hitoyoshi.
Of course, I can't just shake
this fear. But even so...
I want to believe in your words.
Ms. Servant...
Then I will, too!
I'll believe in you, Ms. Servant!
I'll believe in you!
I'll believe in you! I'll believe in you!
I'll believe in you!   I'll believe in you!   I'll believe in you!   I'll believe in you!   I'll believe in you!   I'll believe in you!
Certainly! Leave it to me.
May I try holding him?
Of course!
Is this... mochi?
Only figuratively!
He's actually a dog, all right?
He's so small and warm...
I was really scared of you.
But being with you made me
realize that I was wrong.
Ms. Servant, you're actually
a really good girl!
I understand how you felt now.
It's kind of embarrassing to think
I used to be scared of this.
Katsuda's Sauce
This okonomiyaki is so yummy!
The sauce... The sauce...
The, uh... The dough goes so well
with the cabbage and sauce, and...
Her vocabulary seems to have reverted
to kindergarten level.
Okonomiyaki... really is yummy.
Would you like me to make you
another one, then?
I couldn't possibly trouble you...
That's not what your body language is saying.
Okonomiyaki Flour
It's normal to be a little selfish
about what you like.
So it's normal to want more okonomiyaki!
If you insist, then.
If you have other selfish requests,
keep 'em coming while I'm at it!
Selfish requests...
Consider it a special reward
for getting along with Agemochitaro!
If that's the case, then...
I would like you to give me a name
as well, Master Hitoyoshi.
You want me to give you a name?
Yes... Just like you did with Agemochitaro.
Um, I don't know if I'll be able to
match the mood exactly, but...
Hm... It's tough coming up
with something on the spot.
Ms. Servant, when is your birthday?
I don't know exactly,
but it was during a very cold winter.
I faintly remember being told that
I was born on a record-breaking snowy day.
Winter! You were born in the winter, huh...
Then how about Yuki, for "snow"?
A cold-blooded killer...
Your name is Xue, for "snow."
You know, I love snow!
It's so white and beautiful, and...
Isn't it kinda exciting to see the snow fall?
On top of that, snow is actually warm.
Snow is warm?
I heard about it somewhere.
When the snow gathers on the field,
the dirt and seeds underneath don't freeze,
and when springtime comes, they sprout.
I was thinking, maybe that's because the snow
protects them by keeping them warm.
Why did my body react
the way it did at that time?
Why did I feel such warmth from this world?
Why does this person move my heart so much?
If I stay here...
If I spend more time with him...
I have a feeling I might be able
to find the answer.
Yuki...
Thank you for giving me such
a wonderful name, Master Hitoyoshi.
Yuki. Yuki.
So she smiles like a normal girl, too.
Big Brother
I adopted a dog.
His name's
Agemochitaro.
He's too cute!
Big Brother!
It's me, Riko!